https://www.westernu.edu/westernu-resources/westernu-policy-privacy

Menu
Search...
Quick LinksWesternU homepageProgressIQRegistrarSelf-Service(BanWeb)You PortalSharePointBookstoreAlumniCatalogPumerantz LibraryFinancial AidLEADCampus SecurityResourcesProspective StudentsCurrent StudentsFaculty & StaffGuestsStudent/Employee HealthComputingInstitutional Research And EffectivenessJob OpeningsWesternU NewsReporting Improper ConductCollegesCollege of Osteopathic Medicine of the PacificCOMP - Northwest CampusCollege of Health Sciences – HS,PA,PTCollege of PharmacyCollege of Graduate NursingCollege of Veterinary MedicineCollege of Dental MedicineCollege of OptometryCollege of Podiatric MedicineGraduate College of Biomedical SciencesCommunityWesternU HealthCenter for Disability & Health Policy (CDHP)Faculty Development (CETL)Faculty for Autism Collaboration& Education (FACE)Interprofessional EducationPet Health CareOuttakes CuisineHealth Career LadderPost Jobs for AlumniCenter for InnovationAdministrationUniversity AdministrationBoard of TrusteesAcademic AffairsAcademic SenateHuman ResourcesPublic AffairsUniversity FinancialServices & TreasuryUniversity Risk ManagementBursars OfficeUniversity Policy OfficeResearchOperations DivisionCampusAbout the UniversityContact UsCalendarsCampus DirectoryCampus Maps & DirectionsVirtual ToursEnvironmental Health & SafetyFacilities and Physical PlantMaintenance ScheduleWebsite FeedbackGiving to WesternUBody Donation ProgramWeb Site Map
Dropdown for Search
Dropdown for Menu
Search...
HomeResourcesSite SearchSite mapPoliciesMaintenance ScheduleWebsite Feedback Form
Privacy Policy
Westernu-ResourcesPoliciesPrivacy Policy
Print
Share on Facebook
Share on Twitter
Share by Email
Privacy PolicyCopyright PolicyPrivacy PolicyReporting & Investigation of Alleged Improper ConductWeb Accessibility PolicyGDPR Notice
Western University of Health Sciences (WesternU) reserves the right to use and implement cookies or allow its affiliated entities to do so. The University does not control, nor have any access to, the cookie information affiliated entities may collect. If a Web visitor chooses not to accept these cookies, the browsing experience on some sections of the University’s site and its related sites may be diminished, and some features may not work as intended.
WesternU’s Web site also contains links to external sites. WesternU is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of these Web sites.
In order to better serve the needs of site visitors, WesternU keeps track of certain traffic data. These include the platform used (e.g., Macintosh or PC), browser type (e.g., Netscape or Microsoft Internet Explorer), IP address (or Internet Protocol address, which identifies the visitor’s service provider, but not the visitor personally) and the previous URL (Uniform Resource Locator, or Web address) visited by the visitor before reaching the University’s site. None of these disclose personal information, and the information they do reveal is used exclusively for internal administrative purposes. WesternU does not collect and evaluate this information for specific individuals. WesternU’s Web servers do not automatically record e-mail addresses of the visitors.
WesternU’s search engine collects aggregate search terms for internal reporting and targeted advertising. WesternU monitors aggregate visitor activity on the sites and shares this information with external entities, but at no stage are individual users personally identifiable, nor is any personal information divulged.
WesternU is also involved in organizing and conducting public events, and may, from time to time, use the Web to promote these events and invite prospective attendees to supply certain information about themselves. This demographic information will not be disclosed to any third parties without the consent of the individual or organization concerned.
Web users are sometimes asked to supply personal information, including name, contact information and credit card number, mostly for, but not restricted to, WesternU online stores. Billing information will be used solely for billing purposes and will not otherwise be disclosed.
Whenever a visitor’s identity is requested, the purpose of the inquiry will be indicated before the information is requested. WesternU maintains a strict “No-Spam” policy, which means the University does not sell, rent, or otherwise give e-mail addresses to a third party without consent or as permitted by this Privacy Policy.
Except as stated above, WesternU will not send e-mail to Web visitors that they have not agreed to receive.WesternU will disclose personal information and/or an IP address when required by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to cooperate with the investigations of purported unlawful activities and conform to the edicts of the law or comply with any legal process.
When an order is placed online, WesternU scrambles personal data and credit card information using SSL encryption technology. This makes it virtually impossible for information to be stolen or intercepted while being transferred across the Internet. Upon receipt, orders are encrypted until processed.
By accessing the WesternU sites, Web visitors consent to the collection and use of information by WesternU as specified above. If the University decides to change its privacy policy, it will post those changes on this page to disclose to visitors what information is collected, how it is used, and under what circumstances it will be divulged.
Click for more information on the Privacy Act of 1974.
Queries or questions about this privacy policy should be directed to the Webmaster at webmaster@westernu.edu.
Copyright | Privacy | Accessibility | Feedback
(C) 2020 Western University of Health Sciences. All Rights Reserved
